<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<image>
<url>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/nicons/rsslogo.png</url>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/</link>
</image>
<title>Alahednews</title>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/</link>
<description>Alahednews</description>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Full Speech on the Commemoration of Sayyeda Fatima’s Birth Anniv.</title>
<description>The full speech of Sheikh Qassem during the Sayyeda Fatima [AS] Gathering [13-1-2025]</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/84485/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Full Speech on the Commemoration of the Martyred Scholars on the Path of Liberating Al-Quds</title>
<description>The full speech of Sheikh Qassem during the commemoration of the martyred scholars [5-12-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/84464/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Full Speech on the Memorial for Jihadi Leader Sayyed Haitham Al-Tabatabai and His Companions</title>
<description>The speech of Sheikh Qassem on the memorial ceremony for the great Jihadi leader Sayyed Haytham Al-Tabatabai and his companions [28-11-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/84115/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Full Speech on Martyr’s Day</title>
<description>Speech of Hezbollah Secretary-General Sheikh Naim Qassem on Martyr’s Day [11-11-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/83819/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Speech at the Opening of Ardi Souk Exhibition</title>
<description>Speech by Sheikh Qassem at the opening of the Ardi Market exhibition [2-4-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/83531/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Speech During “Singing and Music: Research by Imam Khamenei” Book Launch</title>
<description>Sheikh Qassem’s speech during launch ceremony of “Singing and Music: Research by Imam Khamenei” [21-10-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/83296/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Full Speech on the Martyrdom Anniv. of Sheikh Nabil Qaouq and Sayyed Suhail Al-Husseini</title>
<description>Speech of Sheikh Qassem on the martyrdom anniversary of Sheikh Nabil Qaouq and Sayyed Suhail Al-Husseini [4-10-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/82929/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Full Speech on the 1st Martyrdom Anniv. of Sayyed Nasrallah and Sayyed Safieddine</title>
<description>Sheikh Qassem full speech on the first martyrdom anniversary of Sayyed Hassan Nasrallah and Sayyed Hashem Safieddine [27, 9, 2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/82896/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Full Speech of Sheikh Qassem on the 1st Martyrdom Anniv. of Leader Hajj Ibrahim Aqil</title>
<description>Sheikh Qassem’s full speech on the first martyrdom anniversary of the jihadi leader Hajj Ibrahim Aqil [Hajj Abdul Qader] [19-9-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/82647/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Full speech of Sheikh Qassem on the One-Week Commemoration of Scholar Sayyed Abbas Al-Moussawi</title>
<description>Sheikh Qassem’s full speech commemorating one week on the passing of Scholar Sayyed Abbas Al-Moussawi [25-8-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/82479/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Full Speech of Shiekh Qassem on Prophet Mohamad’s [PBUH] Birth Anniv. and Islamic Unity Week</title>
<description>The full speech of Sheikh Qassem marking the birth anniversary of Prophet Mohamad and the Islamic Unity Week [10-9-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/82449/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Full Speech of Sheikh Qassem Commemorating the Arbaeen of Imam Hussein [AS]</title>
<description>Sheikh Qassem’s full speech commemorating the Arbaeen of Imam Hussein [AS] [August 15, 2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/82331/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Full Speech of Sheikh Qassem at the Memorial Ceremony for Cmdr. Hajj Ali Karaki</title>
<description>Sheikh Qassem’s full speech at the memorial service for Hajj Abu Al-Fadl [18-7-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/81938/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Full Speech of Sheikh Qassem Marking Forty Days on the Martyrdom of Cmdr. Mohammad Saeed Izadi</title>
<description>Sheikh Qassem’s full speech marking 40 days on the martyrdom of Hajj Ramadan [5-8-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/81885/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Full Speech Marking the 1st Martyrdom Anniv. of Sayyed Fouad Shokor</title>
<description>Full speech of Sheikh Qassem commemorating the 1st martyrdom anniversary of Sayyed Fouad Shokor [30-3-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/81692/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Full Speech of Sheikh Qassem on the 9th Night of Muharram</title>
<description>Sheikh Qassem’s speech on the on the ninth night of the sacred month of Muharram 1447 AH.</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/81264/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>The Full Speech of Sheikh Qassem on the 5th Night of Muharram</title>
<description>Speech of Hezbollah Secretary General Sheikh Naim Qassem on the eve of the fifth of Muharram 1447 AH.</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/81216/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem: We’re To Continue Defending Our Land; Threat Won’t Make Us Surrender</title>
<description>‘We are not concerned with the American-“Israeli” formula that says: either be killed or surrender.’

</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/81209/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Political Part of Sheikh Qassem’s Speech on the 3rd Night of Muharram</title>
<description>The political excerpt from Sheikh Qassem’s speech on the 3rd night of Muharram 1447 AH [28-6-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/81096/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Full Speech on the Resistance and Liberation Day</title>
<description>The full speech of Hezbollah SG Sheikh Naim Qassem on the 25th anniversary of Resistance and Liberation Day [25-5-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/80601/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Full Speech of Sheikh Qassem on 9th Martyrdom Anniv. of Sayyed Mustafa Badreddine</title>
<description>Speech of Hezbollah Secretary General Sheikh Naim Qassem on the 9th martyrdom anniversary of jihadi leader Sayyed Mustafa Badreddine [12-05-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/80378/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Full Speech on Priorities of Lebanon’s Revival and Municipal Elections</title>
<description>Hezbollah SG’s full speech tackling the priorities of Lebanon s revival and the municipal elections [28-04-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/80147/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem’s Full Speech Tackling Lebanon’s Defense Strategy, Overall Situation</title>
<description>The full speech of Sheikh Naim Qassem tackling the defense strategy and overall situation in Lebanon [18-4-2025].</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/79942/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Sheikh Qassem: We Must Face The Dangerous US, ‘Israeli’ Scheme in The Region</title>
<description>Palestine is great because of its people and resistance; it cannot be defeated.

</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/79555/616</link>
</item>
<item>
<title>Speech of Sheikh Qassem during the funeral ceremony of Sayyed Nasrallah and Sayyed Safieddine</title>
<description>Our dear Sayyed led the Resistance to the nation and led the nation to the Resistance.

</description>
<link>https://english.alahednews.com.lb/79105/616</link>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>